Guide to the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Records, 1868-1991 bulk (1981-1990)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio Visual Series, 1963-1990, undated(bulk 1981-1990) (Box 66-68)
  - Audiocassettes Subseries (Box 66-68)
    - Non-Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Activities, Alphabetical (Box 68)
      - Council on Foundations, 35th Annual Conferene, Denver, Colo.: Conference and Welcome Opening Plenary Session, 1984, Apr. (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-14)
      - Council on Foundations, 35th Annual Conferene, Denver, Colo.: Governance and Ethics in Foundation Management, 1984, Apr. (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-15)
      - Council on Foundations, 35th Annual Conferene, Denver, Colo.: Work, Women, and Poverty, 1984, Apr. (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-16)
      - National Women's Studies Association, 7th Annual Convention, University of Maryland: 2nd Plenary: Work, Race, and Class: Making the Links on Theory and Practice, 1985 (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-17)
      - National Women's Studies Association, 8th Annual Convention, University of Maryland, 5th Plenary: Women Working for Change, 1985 (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-18)
      - National Women's Studies Association, 8th Annual Convention, University of Maryland, 6th Plenary: Coalition Building: Strategies for the 1980's, 1986 (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-19)
      - National Women's Studies Association, 8th Annual Convention, University of Maryland, 7th Plenary: Women Working for Change, Women Changing the Future, 1986 (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-20)
      - National Women's Studies Association, 9th Annual Convention, University of Maryland, 8th Plenary: The Political Empowerment of Afro-American Women: Furthering a Feminist Agenda for the 21st Century, 1987 (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-21)
      - National Women's Studies Association, 9th Annual Convention, University of Maryland, 10th Plenary: Spinning Threads of Women's Movement, 1987 (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-22)
      - National Women's Studies Association, 9th Annual Convention, University of Maryland, 11th Plenary: Women and the Constitution: Where Do We Go From Here? 1987 (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-23)
      - Russell, Patricia A. Five W's: What, When, Why, Where, Who undated (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-24)
      - Russell, Patricia A., Hush! Hush! Somebody's Calling My Name, undated (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-25)
      - Russell, Patricia A., When the Brook Meets the River, undated (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-26)
      - Lisa Hazirjian's oral history interviews about SEWEC (Box 68)
        - Davis, Sarah Fields, Durham, N.C. (tape 1), 1994 May 12 (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-27)
        - Davis, Sarah Fields, Durham, N.C. (tape 2), 1994 May 12 (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-28)
        - Lippin, Tobi, 4 April 1994 (tape 1), 1994 April 4 (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-29)
        - Lippin, Tobi, 4 April 1994 (tape 2), 1994 April 4 (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-30)
        - McCreary, Margaret, Durham, N.C., 1993 November 16 and 1994 May 13 (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-31)
        - Brown, Cynthia, Durham, N.C., 1993 November 19 (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-32)
        - North, Jane, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1994 February 9 (Box 68, Case 21, Audio-cassette NS-33)
  - Filmstrips Subseries (Box 68)
    - Come a Long Way to Stand Here: Project on Women, Work, and the Economy, Theology in the Americas (Box 68)
      - Filmstrip 1: Janice Shepard (Box 68)
      - Filmstrip 2: Anna Matilde (Box 68)
      - Filmstrip 3: Augusta Hewlitt (Box 68)
      - Filmstrip 4: Rosie Triplett (Box 68)
      - Tape 1: Corresponds to Filmstrips 1 and 2 (Box 68)
      - Tape 2: Corresponds to Filmstrips 3 and 4 (Box 68)
  - Videocassettes Subseries (Box 68)
    - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Sponsored Activities (Box 68)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Conference on Tourism, Penn Center, S.C., (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-1)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Conference on Tourism, Penn Center, S.C., (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-2)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Conference on Tourism, Penn Center, S.C., (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-3)
      - Conference on Tourism, Penn Center, S.C., (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-4)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Conference on Tourism, Penn Center, S.C., (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-5)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Conference on Tourism, Penn Center, S.C., (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-6)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Conference on Tourism, Penn Center, S.C., (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-7)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Conference on Tourism, Penn Center, S.C., (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-8)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Sea Island Players, In Celebration of Us, Penn Center, S.C., 2 copies, VHS format, footage also on V-7/V-8 (Box 68, Video-cassette V-9)
      - 1987 Nov. 7: Sea Island Players, In Celebration of Us, Penn Center, S.C., 2 copies, VHS format, footage also on V-7/V-8 (Box 68, Video-cassette V-10)
      - 1987 Nov. 17: Hearing: Subcommittee of Labor and Human Resources Committee, United States Senate, Washington, D.C. (VHS Format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-11)
    - Non-Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Activities (Box 68)
      - 1983: Paychecks and Promises: The Impacts of Economic Development, North Carolina Occupational Safety and Health Project, (U-Matic format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-12)
      - 1985: You Got to Move, Cumberland Mountain Educational Cooperative, Inc., (VHS format) (Box 68, Video-cassette V-13)
- Addition to Collection (Box 68)
  - Office Files Series (Box 68)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 68)
      - Bulk mail information, Atlanta, Ga., 1990 (Box 69)
      - Creech and Stafford Insurance Agency, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Georgia Department of Labor, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Inventory list of office equipment, 1990 (Box 69)
  - Correspondence Series (Box 69)
    - Incoming, 1990 Oct.-1991 Feb. (5 folders) (Box 69)
    - Outgoing, 1990 Oct.-1991 Feb. (5 folders) (Box 69)
  - Financial Papers Series (Box 69)
    - Chronological Subseries (Box 69)
      - 1990 Oct.-Nov. (Box 69)
    - Alphabetical Subseries (Box 69)
      - Audits, 1981-1983 (Box 69)
      - Banks: Citizens Trust Bank, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Bank Deposits: Receipts and coupon stubs, 1987 July-1989 Aug. and Receipts and vouchers, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Budgets: 1988-1991 (Box 69)
      - Funding Files: (Box 69)
        - Bishop's Fund for World Relief, 1989-1991 (Box 69)
        - Episcopal Church Center: Coalition for Human Needs, 1987-1990 (Box 69)
        - Levi Strauss Foundation, 1989-1991 (Box 69)
        - Meyer, Bert and Mary Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 69)
        - Presbyterian Hunger Program, 1990-1991 (Box 69)
      - Petty Cash Advances, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Taxes: Internal Revenue Service (Box 69)
        - Reports, 1980-1990 (6 Folders) (Box 69)
        - Tax Returns, 1981-1986 (Box 69)
        - W2s and Transmittals, 1986-1989 (Box 69)
  - Printed Material Series (Box 69)
    - Chronological Subseries (Box 69)
      - 1982-2001 (Box 69)
- Oversize Materials Series (Box 69)
  - Research Director's Files Series (Box 69)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 70)
    - 1983, undated (Opaperfolder 1-2, Box 70)
  - Financial Papers Series (Box 70)
    - Alphabetical Subseries (Box 70)
      - A-T, 1980-1989 (Box 70)
  - Writing Series (Box 70)
    - 1988, undated (Box 70)
  - General Files Series (Box 70)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 70)
    - 1985-1989 (Opaperfolder Folders 1-2, Box 70)
  - Project Files Series (Box 70)
    - undated (Box 70)
  - Highways Projects Files Series (Box 70)
    - United States and State Departments of Transportation Subseries (Box 70)
      - 1989 (Box 70)
    - Alphabetical Subseries (Box 70)
      - Road Construction: Clippings, 1980, undated (Opaperfolder 1-2, Box 70)
  - Subject Files Series (Box 70)
    - 1980-1986, undated (Opaperfolder 1-2, Box 70)
  - Conference Files Series (Box 70)
    - 1989 (Opaperfolder 1-2, Box 70)
  - Organizations Series (Box 70)
    - 1988, undated (Box 70)
    - undated (Opaperfolder 1-2, Box 70)
  - Printed Materials Series (Box 70)
    - Chronological Subseries (Box 70)
      - 1982-1984 (Box 70)
      - 1985-1990, undated (Box 71)
      - 1979-1985, undated (Opaperfolder 1-2, Box 71)
  - Pictures Series (Box 71)
    - Negatives Subseries (Box 71)
      - 1986, undated (Box 70)